Subtitle Provide by dramacool.in Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.in [Admin.@YNG]
Let's see where you run.
دعونا نرى أين تركض.
I will make your Wanxian Sect
سأجعل طائفتك وانشيان
completely vanish from the Four Realms and Eight Wastelands.
تختفي تمامًا من العوالم الأربعة والأراضي الثمانية القاحلة.
Die!
ال!
Enough!
كافٍ!
Courting death.
مغازلة الموت.
Attack!
هجوم!
It wasn't easy getting you out.
لم يكن من السهل إخراجك.
I told you long ago
لقد قلت لك منذ زمن طويل
I'm not someone to mess with.
أنا لست شخصًا يمكن العبث معه.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
I'll leave this to you.
سأترك هذا لك.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
My sister is in danger.
أختي في خطر.
I'm in danger too, you know!
أنا في خطر أيضًا، هل تعلم؟
Little Saint King of Wanxian Sect,
الملك القديس الصغير لطائفة وانشيان،
it's time to say goodbye.
حان الوقت لقول وداعا.
You—
أنت-
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm here to purge the sect.
أنا هنا لتطهير الطائفة.
But not just Wanxian Sect.
ولكن ليس فقط طائفة وانكسيان.
Demon Sea will disappear too.
بحر الشيطان سوف يختفي أيضا
Shameless!
وقح!
I'm a smart person.
أنا شخص ذكي.
Of course I agree with the smart approach.
بالطبع أنا أتفق مع النهج الذكي.
So,
لذا،
you're accepting my proposal?
هل تقبل اقتراحي؟
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
To make friends.
لتكوين صداقات.
Wha—what...
ماذا؟
You... you...
أنت... أنت...
Sorry.
آسف.
With Lord Xiaoyao's wisdom, you should understand
مع حكمة اللورد شياوياو، يجب أن تفهم
if the Wanxian Sect is destroyed,
إذا تم تدمير طائفة وانشيان،
can you really coexist peacefully with Demon Sea?
هل يمكنك حقًا التعايش بسلام مع بحر الشيطان؟
That's my own business.
هذا شأني الخاص.
You—
أنت-
I can help you wipe out Demon Sea.
يمكنني مساعدتك في القضاء على بحر الشيطان.
Wanxian Sect isn't as strong as Demon Sea.
طائفة وانشيان ليست قوية مثل بحر الشيطان.
So we'll definitely ask for less than them.
لذلك سنطلب بالتأكيد أقل منهم.
Think it over carefully.
فكر في الأمر جيدا.
Once we enter the Primordial Secret Realm tomorrow,
بمجرد دخولنا إلى عالم الأسرار البدائية غدًا،
it's not too late to decide then.
ليس من المتأخر بعد أن تقرر.
I'll close the door for you.
سأغلق الباب لك.
But since you could backstab Rahou,
ولكن بما أنك قد تطعن راحو في ظهره،
I doubt you'd truly ally with me.
أنا أشك في أنك ستتحالف معي حقًا.
You guessed right.
لقد خمنت بشكل صحيح.
So,
لذا،
guess what I'll do next.
أعتقد ماذا سأفعل بعد ذلك.
If I were you,
لو كنت مكانك
I'd destroy the Wanxian Sect.
سأدمر طائفة وانشيان.
Rule alone.
حكم وحيدا.
You guessed right.
لقد خمنت بشكل صحيح.
You should've teamed up with Rahou.
كان ينبغي عليك التعاون مع راهو.
That guy's not too bright.
هذا الرجل ليس ذكيا جدا.
I approached him.
اقتربت منه.
He didn't agree.
لم يوافق.
What an idiot.
يا له من أحمق!
Since you already knew
بما أنك عرفت بالفعل
I figured out your plan,
لقد توصلت إلى خطتك،
aren't you afraid
ألا تخاف؟
I'll call for reinforcements?
سأطلب التعزيزات؟
What reinforcements could you have?
ما هي التعزيزات التي يمكن أن تكون لديك؟
Do you know
هل تعلم
I've been to Night King City?
هل ذهبت إلى مدينة الملك الليلي؟
Night King City never gets involved in the Four Realms and Eight Wastelands
لا تتدخل مدينة ملك الليل أبدًا في العوالم الأربعة والأراضي القاحلة الثمانية
or any sect's conflicts.
أو أي صراعات طائفية.
Even if Night King City's people dare to come,
حتى لو تجرأ شعب مدينة ملك الليل على المجيء،
I'll kill them too.
سأقتلهم أيضاً
Who said they were going to kill me?
من قال أنهم سيقتلونني؟
That white-haired guy.
هذا الرجل ذو الشعر الأبيض.
Jun Wushang from Night King City.
جون ووشانغ من مدينة ملك الليل.
Don't you guys avoid
لا تتجنبوا يا رفاق
all sect conflicts?
كل الصراعات الطائفية؟
That's why I came alone today.
لهذا السبب جئت وحدي اليوم.
I'm not representing Night King City.
أنا لا أمثل مدينة ملك الليل.
You—
أنت-
Lord, go on, go on.
يا رب، استمر، استمر.
These two aren't as strong as you said.
هذين ليسا قويين كما قلت.
If I'd known, I wouldn't have come myself.
لو كنت أعلم لم أكن لأأتي بنفسي.
I didn't expect that either.
ولم أتوقع ذلك أيضًا.
Rahou, as Demon Sea's Sect Leader,
راهو، بصفته زعيم طائفة بحر الشيطان،
is so weak.
إنه ضعيف جدًا.
Wait, that's not right.
انتظر، هذا ليس صحيحا.
This Rahou is a fake.
هذا راهو مزيف.
So where's the real Rahou?
إذن أين هو راهو الحقيقي؟
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
The Dao River opened early!
تم افتتاح نهر داو مبكرا!
Hurry up and go!
اسرع واذهب!
Make sure to get the Brahma Fruit!
تأكد من الحصول على فاكهة البراهما!
I understand now.
انا أفهم الآن.
All paths under heaven,
كل الطرق تحت السماء،
return to the Great Dao.
العودة إلى الداو العظيم.
The Great Dao you have pursued
الطريق العظيم الذي سعيت إليه
is the ultimate.
هو النهائي.
It is the limit of cultivation.
إنه حد الزراعة.
It is the end of the Great Dao.
إنها نهاية الداو العظيم.
The Great Dao has its limits.
إن الطريق العظيم له حدوده.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
The founding of the Four Realms and Eight Wastelands
تأسيس العوالم الأربعة والأراضي الثمانية القاحلة
happened countless ages ago.
لقد حدث ذلك منذ عصور لا تعد ولا تحصى.
Nine supreme beings emerged in the universe.
ظهرت تسعة كائنات عليا في الكون.
They created heaven and earth.
لقد خلقوا السماء والأرض.
So,
لذا،
their Dao became the Great Dao.
وأصبح طريقهم الطريق الأعظم.
Ridiculous.
سخيف.
You.
أنت.
Your Great Dao is a joke.
طريقتك العظيمة هي مجرد نكتة.
You, just at the Pudu Realm,
أنت، فقط في عالم بودو،
what do you know of the Great Dao?
ماذا تعرف عن الداو العظيم؟
Let me tell you now
دعني أخبرك الآن
what the true Great Dao is.
ما هو الداو العظيم الحقيقي؟
The Nine Emperors are powerful,
الأباطرة التسعة أقوياء،
but they do not represent the Great Dao.
لكنهم لا يمثلون الداو العظيم.
They knew nothing of martial arts before them.
لم يكونوا يعرفون شيئًا عن الفنون القتالية قبلهم.
And the new martial arts after the Nine Emperors,
والفنون القتالية الجديدة بعد الأباطرة التسعة،
they do not understand either.
وهم لا يفهمون أيضًا.
Such incomplete things
مثل هذه الأشياء غير المكتملة
cannot be called the Great Dao.
لا يمكن أن يطلق عليه اسم الداو العظيم.
Besides,
بجانب،
the Nine Emperors all had differences.
كان للأباطرة التسعة اختلافات.
Does that mean
هل هذا يعني
there are nine Great Daos in this world?
هل هناك تسعة داوس عظيمة في هذا العالم؟
Go on.
إستمر.
Past Dao.
الطريق الماضي.
Present Dao.
داو الحاضر.
Future Dao.
داو المستقبل.
Simply put,
ببساطة،
summarize the past,
تلخيص الماضي،
comprehend the present,
فهم الحاضر،
and foresee the future.
وتوقع المستقبل.
Only when the three Daos unite is it the true Great Dao.
فقط عندما تتحد الطواويس الثلاثة يكون هذا هو الطاو العظيم الحقيقي.
Who can achieve the Great Dao you speak of?
من يستطيع تحقيق الداو العظيم الذي تتحدث عنه؟
No one can.
لا أحد يستطيع ذلك.
So in this world,
لذا في هذا العالم،
there is no need for a true Great Dao.
ليست هناك حاجة إلى داو عظيم حقيقي.
What? What?
ماذا؟ ماذا؟
Blind faith in the Great Dao
الإيمان الأعمى بالداو العظيم
is worse than having no Dao at all.
أسوأ من عدم وجود داو على الإطلاق.
Without the Great Dao,
بدون الداو العظيم،
everywhere is the Great Dao.
في كل مكان هناك الداو العظيم.
Sheer nonsense.
محض هراء.
Without the Great Dao,
بدون الداو العظيم،
everywhere becomes the Great Dao.
في كل مكان يصبح الداو العظيم.
everywhere is the Great Dao.
في كل مكان هناك الداو العظيم.
I have understood.
لقد فهمت.
I have been trapped by the Great Dao all my life.
لقد كنت محاصرًا بالداو العظيم طوال حياتي.
Obsessed, yet fruitless.
مهووس، ولكن بلا جدوى.
Now the Great Dao is clear.
الآن أصبح الطريق العظيم واضحا.
I must leave now.
يجب علي أن أغادر الآن.
The secret of the Primordial Secret Realm
سر عالم الأسرار البدائية
has finally met the right person.
لقد التقى أخيرا بالشخص المناسب.
It's yours.
إنها لك.
Lin Yue.
لين يو.
My father said
قال والدي
he can only help you this one last time.
لا يمكنه مساعدتك إلا هذه المرة الأخيرة.
No matter what you do in the future,
بغض النظر عما تفعله في المستقبل،
don't involve him or Night King City.
لا تشركه أو تشرك مدينة ملك الليل.
He helped me this time,
لقد ساعدني هذه المرة،
and I am deeply grateful.
وأنا ممتن للغاية.
Let him have no more worries.
لا داعي للقلق بعد الآن.
I won't trouble him again.
لن أزعجه مرة أخرى.
Then,
ثم،
I'm going back today.
سأعود اليوم.
There are many matters in Night King City.
هناك العديد من الأمور في مدينة ملك الليل.
I can't leave him alone.
لا أستطيع أن أتركه بمفرده.
You've matured after this journey.
لقد نضجت بعد هذه الرحلة.
Now you understand your father's difficulties.
الآن فهمت الصعوبات التي واجهها والدك.
Lin Yue.
لين يو.
Then,
ثم،
if you have time in the future,
إذا كان لديك الوقت في المستقبل،
you can come find me in Night King City.
يمكنك أن تجدني في مدينة ملك الليل.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Did you get the Brahma Fruit?
هل حصلت على فاكهة البراهما؟
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
Half of it.
نصفها.
Even with the Brahma Fruit,
حتى مع فاكهة البراهما،
it might not be enough to defeat the Seven Sins Demon Emperor.
ربما لا يكون ذلك كافيا لهزيمة إمبراطور شيطان الخطايا السبع.
Now Rahou has stolen half of it.
الآن سرق راهو نصفها.
Doesn't that mean all our efforts were wasted?
ألا يعني هذا أن كل جهودنا ذهبت سدى؟
I'll find a way.
سأجد طريقة.
There's no time left.
لم يتبق وقت .
The day of the Holy Maiden's sacrifice
يوم تضحية العذراء المقدسة
has been moved up.
لقد تم نقله إلى الأعلى.